const STORE = [
    {
        question: 'Which of the following nicknames was Ben Hogan NOT known as?',
        answers: [
            'The Hawk',
            'Bantam Ben',
		    'Big Ben',
		    'The Wee Iceman',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Big Ben',
        extraInfo: 'Hogan was never known as big ben.',
    },
    {
        question: 'Ben Hogan served in which branch of the US Military?',
        answers: [
            'Army',
            'Navy',
		    'Air Force',
		    'Coast Guard',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Air Force',
        extraInfo: 'Ben Hogan served in the Air Force',
    },
    {
        question: 'In 1950, Hogan famously used what uncommon club to win the U.S Open Championship during the 18 hole playoff?',
        answers: [
            'a rescue wood',
            'a driver from the fairway',
		    '1 iron',
		    '2 iron',
        ],
        correctAnswer: '1 iron',
        extraInfo: 'Hogan famously used his 1 iron in the playoff. There is a plaque where the shot took place 200 yards from the green.',
    },
    {
        question: 'Ben Hogan is known by amateur golfers and professionals alike as the greatest ever at what aspect of the game of golf?',
        answers: [
            'Ball-striking',
            'Putting',
		    'Teaching',
		    'Rescue shots',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Ball-striking',
        extraInfo: 'His ball-striking abilities were second-to-none.',
    },
    {
        question: 'How many Major Championships did Ben Hogan win?',
        answers: [
            '11',
            '9',
		    '7',
		    '5',
        ],
        correctAnswer: '9',
        extraInfo: 'Hogan won a total of 9 Major Championships',
    },
    {
        question: `What was the title of Ben Hogan's instructional book?`,
        answers: [
            'The Four Lessons',
            'The Five Lessons',
		    'The Six Lessons',
		    'The Seven Lessons',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'The Five Lessons',
        extraInfo: `His instructional book on how to best emulate his own swing was entited, 'The Five Lessons'`,
    },
    {
        question: 'Of the following, which is not a major section in his instructional book?',
        answers: [
            'The fundamentals',
            'Preparation',
		    'Stance and Posture',
		    'The swing',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Preparation',
        extraInfo: `'Preparation' was not a part of his instructional book.`,
    },
    {
        question: `What was the title of the biographical film detailed Ben's life starring Glen Ford?`,
        answers: [
            'Hogan',
            'The Masters',
		    'Hickok Belt',
		    'Follow the Sun',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Follow the Sun',
        extraInfo: `'Follow the Sun' is the title of the biopic about Hogan's life.`,
    },
    {
        question: 'Hogan graduated from what high school?',
        answers: [
            'E.L. Paschal High School',
            'R.L. Paschal High School',
		    'P.L. Paschal High School',
		    `He didn't graduate from high school.`,
        ],
        correctAnswer:  `He didn't graduate from high school.`,
        extraInfo: 'Hogan dropped out of R.L. Paschal High School in his final semester',
    },
    {
        question: 'Ben Hogan and who else were the only two golfers to ever receive a ticker-tape parade?',
        answers: [
            'Gene Sarazen',
            'Tiger Woods',
		    'Phil Mickelson',
		    'Sergio Garcia',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Gene Sarazen',
        extraInfo: 'Hogan received a ticker-tape parade upon his return from England after winning the British Open. Gene Sarazen was the only other golfer to receive this honor.',
    },
]